
import '../models/question.dart';


// Question bank for playing with and displaying
final List<Question> questions = [

  Question(topic: 'Topic 1', question: 'Question 1', answer: 'Answer 1'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 1', question: 'Question 2', answer: 'Answer 2'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 1', question: 'Question 3', answer: 'Answer 3'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 1', question: 'Question 4', answer: 'Answer 4'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 1', question: 'Question 5', answer: 'Answer 5'),

  Question(topic: 'Topic 2', question: 'Question 1', answer: 'Answer 1'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 2', question: 'Question 2', answer: 'Answer 2'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 2', question: 'Question 3', answer: 'Answer 3'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 2', question: 'Question 4', answer: 'Answer 4'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 2', question: 'Question 5', answer: 'Answer 5'),

  Question(topic: 'Topic 3', question: 'Question 1', answer: 'Answer 1'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 3', question: 'Question 2', answer: 'Answer 2'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 3', question: 'Question 3', answer: 'Answer 3'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 3', question: 'Question 4', answer: 'Answer 4'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 3', question: 'Question 5', answer: 'Answer 5'),

  Question(topic: 'Topic 4', question: 'Question 1', answer: 'Answer 1'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 4', question: 'Question 2', answer: 'Answer 2'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 4', question: 'Question 3', answer: 'Answer 3'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 4', question: 'Question 4', answer: 'Answer 4'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 4', question: 'Question 5', answer: 'Answer 5'),

  Question(topic: 'Topic 5', question: 'Question 1', answer: 'Answer 1'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 5', question: 'Question 2', answer: 'Answer 2'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 5', question: 'Question 3', answer: 'Answer 3'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 5', question: 'Question 4', answer: 'Answer 4'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 5', question: 'Question 5', answer: 'Answer 5'),

  Question(topic: 'Topic 6', question: 'Question 1', answer: 'Answer 1'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 6', question: 'Question 2', answer: 'Answer 2'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 6', question: 'Question 3', answer: 'Answer 3'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 6', question: 'Question 4', answer: 'Answer 4'),
  Question(topic: 'Topic 6', question: 'Question 5', answer: 'Answer 5'),



];